Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1104, Education Division; Records apap132
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files, 1979-2000; Undated; 2; 3.0 cubic ft.
  - Election Materials, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Grievance Handbook: Step By Step Guide, Undated (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Ground Rules: 1995 & 1999 Negotiations Between GSEU and the State of New York (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - GSEU Active File: Mainly Election Issues, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - GSEU/CWA Local 1188 Counterproposals to State of New York, 1995 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - GSEU Election Report of the Election Committee Chair, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - GSEU Local 1188 Demands Presented to NYS for Successor Agreement to 1995-1999 Collective Bargaining Agreement (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Legal Cases, i.e. Improper Practice Charges, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Legal Papers: Issues Between CWA, GSEU, and PERB, 1987; 1991 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Legal Papers: Issues Between CWA, GSEU, and PERB, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Letter-Writing to State Legislators, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Local 1188 Temporary Administration Debate, 1999 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Local Filing System Methods, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1984-1986; 1992 (Box 2 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 1-3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes, Undated (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes: Comprehensive Fee, 1999 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes Notebook, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Meeting Notes, Undated (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Membership Graphs by Center School, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Membership Meetings and Recruitment, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Memorandum of Agreement Between GSEU and SUNY University Libraries, 2000 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Between NYS and GSEU Local 1188, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Mobilizing Calendars and Agenda, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Morning Meeting Task Lists, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Negotiating Briefs, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Organizing Reports from SUNY University Centers, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Organizing Reports from SUNY University Centers, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Organizing Reports - Statewide, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Reimbursement Paperwork, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Renegotiation of CWA Affiliation Agreement, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Resolution Between GSEU Executive Committee and its Negotiators, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Secret Ballot Forms and Information, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Statewide Roundup, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Steward Correspondence, 1984; 1994; 1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Steward Election Verification, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Steward Meeting Minutes, 1982; 1993-1994 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Steward Subcommittee Meetings, Lists, and Members @ Buffalo, 1995; 1997 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Steward Tasks - Signing up the Nonmember, Phone Script, Undated (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Stewards and Representatives List, Albany, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Stewards Manual, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Stewards Manual, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Stewards Resource Manual, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Stewards Resource Manual: Building the Union on the Job, Revised, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Subcommittees of the Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Weekly Staff Reports, ca. 1995 (Box 3 (2-Statewide Executive Committee Administrative Files), Folder 39)
- SUNY Center School Administrative Files, 1974-2000; Undated; 3; 3.2 cubic ft.
  Arranged in subseries by school, then alphabetically within each school.
  This series is divided into subseries by SUNY center school; each contains meeting minutes, correspondence, organizing reports, contact lists and other papers that show the daily and monthly operations of the SUNY school divisions of the GSEU Local 1104. There is considerable evidence of the connection between statewide executive committee members and the local branches of the GSEU as they worked to solve issues including parking fees, technology fees, tuition waivers, fair wage, and more. As noted above, there are considerably more files for SUNY Buffalo than there are for the three other schools, probably due in large part to Buffalos role as the birthplace of the union movement.
  - SUNY Albany, 1983-2000; 3.1
    - Committee Activist Lists, Undated (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 1)
    - Contact Lists, 1993-1997 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 2)
    - Contact Lists, Undated (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 3)
    - Correspondence-Attorney Peter Henner, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 4)
    - Correspondence-General, 1983; 1992-1992; 1995 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 5)
    - Correspondence-General, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 6)
    - Correspondence-General, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 7)
    - Early Organizing Reports and Academic Department Lists, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 8)
    - Living Wage Campaign, Undated (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 9)
    - Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1992; 1995; 1999 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 10)
    - Member Lists, Undated (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 11-12)
    - Organizing Binder - Cooperative Efforts with GSO, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 13-14)
    - Organizing Binder - Memos, Agendas, Miscellaneous Finances, 1999 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 15)
    - Organizing Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - SUNY Binghamton, 1974-2000; 3.2
    - Contact Lists, 1983; Undated (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 17)
    - Correspondence-General, 1974-1993 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 18)
    - Correspondence-General, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 19)
    - Correspondence-General, 1996-1997; 2000 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 20)
    - Early Organizing Reports and Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 21)
    - Health Insurance Proclamation, 1990 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 22)
    - Meeting Minutes and Agenda, 1992; 1994; 1999 (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 23)
    - Organizing Reports, 1982-1983; 1993-1995; Undated (Box 1 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - SUNY Buffalo, 1982-1999; 3.3
    - Academic Department Fact-Finding Survey, 1982 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 1)
    - Active Graduate and Teaching Assistants, 1985 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 2)
    - Annual Report: Graduate History Students Association, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 3)
    - Attorneys Lipsitz, Green, Fahringer, etc.  Letters, Reports, and Affidavits, 1975; 1982 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 4)
    - Buffalo Elections Committee for Binghamton Delegate Assembly, 1983 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 5)
    - Buffalo Womens Caucus, 1984 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 6)
    - Contact Lists, 1983-1987; Undated (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 7)
    - Contact Lists, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 8)
    - Contact Mobilization, 1996 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 9)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Architecture and Planning School, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Biology Department, 1995 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Chemistry Department, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Comprehensive Fee Grievances, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - Contract Interpretations, 1994 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - Contract Negotiation Letters of Support, 1996 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Department Stewards, 1982; 1984 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Elimination of Library Science GA Positions, 1995 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - Faculty Letters of Union Support, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - General, 1975-1977; 1981-1982 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - General, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - General, 1985-1986; 1990 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - General, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - General, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - General, 1996-1999 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - General, Undated (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Center for Urban Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - Millard Fillmore College, 1994 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 28)
    - Correspondence - President Steven Sample, 1982 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 29)
    - Correspondence - Middle States Association Report, 1983 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 30)
    - Correspondence - Modern Language & Literature, Policy Changes, 1995-1997 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 31)
    - Correspondence - National Association of Graduate-Professional Students, Inc., 1991 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 32)
    - Correspondence - Provost William R. Greiner, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 33)
    - Correspondence - State Budget Issues, 1976; 1982 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 34)
    - Correspondence - Third-Party Memos and Letters, 1984-1985; 1991-1992 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 35)
    - Correspondence - United University Professions, 1982; 1984; 1992 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 36)
    - Department GAs/TAs/RAs Independent of GSEU Membership, 1982 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 37)
    - Department/Membership Tallies, 1984; 1992; 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 38)
    - Departmental G.A./T.A. Information, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 39)
    - Early Organizing Materials - Letters, Flyers, and News Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 40)
    - Freedom of Information Requests, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 41)
    - Friends of the GSEU, 1998 (Box 2 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 42)
    - GA/TA/RA Ad-Hoc Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 1)
    - GA/TA/RA Ad-Hoc Committee, 1982 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 2)
    - Graduate and Professional Education Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 3)
    - Graduate Student Association - Steward Recruitment to GSEU, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 4)
    - GSA Senate Committee, 1985 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 5)
    - GSEU and the Soloman Amendment, 1983 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 6)
    - GSEU Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 7)
    - GSEU Membership Meeting Agenda, ca. 1998 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 8)
    - Health Benefits Orientation Rap, Buffalo, 1998 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 9)
    - Health Insurance Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 10)
    - Labor Management Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 11)
    - Labor Management Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 12)
    - Labor Management Meetings & Agendas - Leslie Rockenbach, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 13)
    - Meeting Minutes - General, 1982-1983; 1992-1994; 1996-2000 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 14)
    - Meeting Notebook, Undated (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 15)
    - Membership Drives, 1983 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 16)
    - Membership Master List, 1998 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 17)
    - Mobilizers: Letters, Memos, and Contact Lists, 1998; Undated (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 18)
    - Organizing Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 19)
    - Organizing Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 20)
    - Organizing Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 21)
    - Orientation Materials, 1991 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 22)
    - Press Contacts, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 23)
    - Ramifications of Unionization Committee, 1985 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 24)
    - Steering Committee Elections, 1995 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 25)
    - Steering Committee Meetings, 1983 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 26-28)
    - Steering Committee Meetings, 1984 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 29)
    - Steering Committee Meetings, 1994 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 30)
    - Steering Committee Meetings, 1995 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 31)
    - Steering Committee Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 32)
    - Steering Committee, 1998; Undated (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 33)
    - Steward Assembly, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 34)
    - Stipend Data, 1989 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 35)
    - Tuition Waver Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 36)
    - Weekly Updates, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - SUNY Stony Brook, 1981-1999; 3.4
    - Campus Reports to University Senate, 1987 January (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 1)
    - Contact Lists, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 2)
    - Contact Negotiations, 1999 (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - General, 1982-1989 (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - General, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 5)
    - Graduate Student Organization Bulletin, Vol. 1 #1, ca. 1981 (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 6)
    - Graduate Student Organization Self-Study, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 7)
    - Graduate Student Rights and Responsibilities/ Grievances and Appeals, Undated (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 8)
    - GSEU Information Handbook, Undated (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 9)
    - GSO Presentation to Administration - Graduate & Research InitiativeAcademic Department Fact-Finding Survey, Undated (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 10)
    - Meeting Minutes and Agenda, 1982; 1991-1995; Undated (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 11)
    - Organizing Reports, 1984-1993 (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 12)
    - Reports: What Can be Done to Improve Graduate Student Welfare (undated) and A History of Graduate Student Unionization at Stonybrook Until 1980 (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 13)
    - Signed Members, 1994 October (Box 4 (3-SUNY Center School Administrative Files), Folder 14)
- Financial Papers, 1982-2000; Undated; 4; 0.8 cubic ft.
  This series is a mix of statewide and individual school financial papers. Each folder is labeled accordingly so researchers can tell at a glance if a folder is related to a specific school or if it is executive committee information. Topics include cash flow reports, expense sheets, tax information, and budgeting guidelines. There is a select amount of material for each school and the executive committee, but no one category has a large amount of financial data, which overall is very scarce for this group.
  - Albany: Cash Flow Report, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 1)
  - Albany: Expense Sheets, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 2)
  - Albany: General Financial Correspondence/ Booklets, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 3)
  - Albany: Taxes/ Payroll/ Tuition Waivers, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 4)
  - Beirne Scholarship Information, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 5)
  - Blank Expense Forms, Undated (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 6)
  - Budget Issues: State of New York and United University Professions, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 7)
  - Budget Reports, Miscellaneous, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Budget Proposals and Corresponding Memos/Letters, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 9)
  - Buffalo: Budget Requests and Updates, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 10)
  - Buffalo Expenses, 1982-1984 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Expenses, 1995-1999 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 13)
  - Buffalo: GA/TA Stipends, 1982 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 14)
  - Buffalo: GA/TA Tax Status, 1982-1983; 1987 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 15)
  - Buffalo Money Issues: Credit Union, Dues, Raises, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 16)
  - Buffalo: Personal Reimbursements, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 1)
  - Buffalo: Petty Cash Records, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 2)
  - Buffalo: Salary Withholding Program, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 3)
  - Campus Profiles Booklet: Financial and Related Information, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 4)
  - CWA Dues Advances and GSEU Disbursement History, 1999 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Budgeting Guidelines, Undated (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Expenditures and Resource Planning, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Internal Budget Memos and Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Treasurers Report, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Treasurers Report w/ Resource Allocation Scenarios, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 10)
  - Expenses Statements - Kathleen Sims, 2000 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 11)
  - Financial Report/ Analysis and Budget: GSEU/CWA Local 1188, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 12)
  - FPI Budget Coalition Meeting Agenda and Packet, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 13)
  - GSEU Payroll Dates and Reimbursement Forms, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 14)
  - Monthly Reimbursement Guidelines, 1993; 2000 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 15)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Dues Invoice, 1999 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 16)